Zack, uh, injured up like PJ Jules got
hurt.
>> Yeah, PJ will be week to week with an
ankle.
>> Then how did Osai come out of that game?
>> Laceration, so I think he'll be okay.
We'll see where it is. He might be
limited early in the week, but was a
laceration.
>> No change on Trey status would expect.
>> Uh, Trey will be out, so he he's seen
another specialist today and we'll see
where that goes.
>> Is the Germaine Burton suspension just
for that game?
So, we're we're releasing Germaine
today.
>> What led to that decision?
>> Um, just decision to make. We just made
it. We're going to release him and move
on and wish him the best.
>> How frustrating was it that you just
pick never materialized? Like the talent
y'all saw when y'all drafted him just
never came to fruition?
>> Yeah, I think everybody worked really
hard at it and wish him the best.
Hopefully, he gets to change his scenery
and can do good things for him.
what pre uh precipitated his suspension
on Saturday?
>> I won't get into that. We're going to
release him today.
>> Optimism for Shamar. Is he eligible to
come off this week?
>> We'll see. We'll get to Wednesday and
then sort through how we want to
approach it this week. So, we'll get to
Wednesday and make a decision on that.
>> With Trey, is that going to is that
change? Is there a chance he could come
back at some point or what what is he
>> I'm not sure yet, but we'll get more
information on that today.
>> But he's up, but he's out for this week.
>> He's out for this week.
>> Um any uh I guess you just got to make a
move receiver or
>> uh we'll see. We'll see where we end up
with with the roster spots. So, um
anyway, I'm not going to speak too soon
on that. We've got till Wednesday or
really later this week to see how it
sorts out. Do you have more clarity on
what specific? I know it's been like
back, hip, pelvis on Trey. What do you
know have more details on what exactly
he's dealing with?
>> Yes, kind of all that.
>> Okay.
>> Covering tight ends has been probably a
sore spot for you guys. What can you do
to fix that?
>> There's a couple things. I mean, we we
can be better on some of those snaps.
Um, not buying so much on the action in
front of them. Um, and there's other
ways. I know Al's trying to help him
schematically as well. So each one's a
little bit of its a unique look because
you might be in a different coverage, it
might be a different look, might be a
different way that they got the tight
end there, but um certainly has been
something that's bit us and we've got to
work like crazy to rectify it.
>> How much of it is two rookie linebackers
is going to teams are going to come in
and try to pick on that and that has
kind of turned into a thing in of
itself.
>> That happens sometimes. I think they've
they've continued to gain the experience
through it and so some things that maybe
got them earlier in the season, they've
done a great job reacting to it. Um,
this is one that, you know, didn't work
well for us in this last game, but um,
feel good about how we can rectify that
and continue to improve to stop it.
>> Did you expect or hope that it would be
at a better level though by this point
in the season?
>> Well, there's there's two elements to
it. They're they're doing a much better
job stopping the run obviously and so
when teams are utilizing that to your
advantage, um, there's some big plays to
be had in the pass game. That that's
really team that comes in and runs the
ball really well. Typically, they're a
good play action team behind it when
they've got a quarterback like they do
and they got the tight ends they do. So,
it's hand in hand of you played a team
who's who's first in the league in
rushing. So, how you gonna stop that?
You got to commit to stopping it. And at
times, it's going to free up some guys
behind you. You don't want it to happen.
We have tools to make sure that doesn't
happen, but it happened. And and the
reality is they're a really good run
team and they can capitalize on it
sometimes and get some big explosives
off it in the pass game. It's fair to
say the tight end issue has been kind of
the biggest factor in what's gone
particularly sideways on defense.
>> Well, that's that's again, it's both.
It's I think we've been better against
the run as of late these last couple
weeks. And so to combat that, some teams
are hard action and trying to get the
tight end to slip behind you. And um
again, I'm not saying we we've done a
great job against it. Um there are snaps
where we have done a great job where you
don't even notice it because it's been
taken away. And there's been some times
where we get up on explosives and and we
have to be much better there.
>> How can Demetrius Knight specifically
play better? What are the biggest things
you're looking for for growth from him?
>> How can he play better?
>> Yeah. What what are the biggest things
you're looking for?
>> I I think for both those guys it's again
just continue to gain experience with
each snap and don't make the same
mistake twice and learn from what you're
seeing. And I think they do a great job
with their preparation through the week
where they've gained a lot of confidence
through what they've seen and the guys
around them have gained a lot of
confidence and some of the adjustments
they got to make on the move. they
they've done an excellent job growing in
that area. Um and again, they're on
games, you know, I I've said this
before, they're on games, you know,
eight and 13 or whatever it is starting
and um we played some guys that have 100
starts under their belt. And so, again,
that's that's one of those key positions
where the experience really helps you,
the more you can gain. And so, we're
trying to get that experience to them as
quickly as possible so that the payoff
can be as quickly as possible because we
see high-end trades from those guys. And
um I think they're making really good
progress and I still have really high
hopes for them and proud of the growth
that they've had and it doesn't mean
that there's not going to be some
hiccups along the way but um they're
made of the right stuff and we'll
continue to invest him.
>> Was there any consideration in releasing
earlier in the year? I mean he hasn't
been active all year.
>> We just decided to release him today.
>> One thing that you guys took a lot of
pride in Zack was fourminute offense the
last several years. curious. Um, weren't
able to pull it off, I'm sure, the way
you wanted to execute yesterday. How do
you think you guys have fared in that
this year?
>> Fourminute off.
>> I haven't had an opportunity um and
really weren't there yesterday, you
know, with with Josh Allen on the other
side. There's 555 left on the clock. We
need to go score and trying to run clock
at the same time, but but we were not in
a 4-minute mode where there was going to
be one possession left in the game. Um,
and so obviously we didn't finish that
game the way we wanted to and it was
disappointing because we had we we were
in a good spot. We played the game the
right way for a long time and we just
didn't finish those last six minutes
>> with Germaine obviously I mean over the
training camp in the offseason, you
know, he was praised a lot for his
progress and and maturity that he's
shown. What kind of happened in did
anything happen in between that period
and now that just kind of didn't ever
let him get on the field? No, I think I
I just wish him the best, you know, and
so again, we made the decision we made
today and pulling for him to go make an
opportunity for himself somewhere else.
>> You were looking at the coach just on it
was such a such a big and odd play to
pick six. Just what was your take when
you look at it on paper?
>> It's a great play. It's a unique play.
It's rare uh that it happens. Uh the
circumstances were were rare. um a bunch
of things colliding at one time and
ended with with Christian Benford making
an outstanding play for a corner. Great
awareness by him, great ball skills by
him, great finish by him. Um that's
that's the number one takeaway. You can
look at that play a million different
ways. Um
and you know, at the end of the day, he
they brought a corner blitz and he made
an outstanding adjustment to the play
and picked it off and scored.
>> I mean, that was that was the unique
thing, right? Because it was kind of a I
think he thought it was a run and he was
surprised when Joe threw it. So, it just
seemed like a lot of kind of weird
signs.
>> They've had a lot of success. I think
that they brought 26, you know,
throughout the year and um brought a
couple against us, some we handled
better. That one was a just unique spot
and without getting too much detail on
it was a unique play and he made a great
play on it.
>> What did you think of T's play yesterday
and what he has been playing through and
the
>> effort that he has made to get himself
back on the field going through the
protocol and all that?
>> He made some enormous plays for us. um
in the game and so again he he comes up
really big in big moments and he's a guy
that Joe can trust and [clears throat]
um so so proud of the way they handle
all that.
>> There were a lot of conversations about
um obviously he had went through the
protocol to clear clear the protocol.
What's that uh conversation like between
the independent spotter Matt and you in
terms of how available a player is once
he goes through that?
>> I'm just told if he's available or not.
And so I think what happened yesterday
was obviously there's some that looked
bad. He felt good throughout it is is
what I've you know gained throughout the
game and postgame obviously. Um he did
this morning and last night have
symptoms again. So we will put him back
in the protocol. Um but again just I
talked to T one 101 too on when you feel
this because you're you're worried about
the guy. Okay. Did you feel it during
the game? No, I felt fine. You know I
took hits um got up and felt fine and
and then after the fact reported that he
he felt concussion symptoms. So, we'll
put him back in the protocol and we'll
go through that this week.
>> Is there any I mean, how how what was
your reaction like uh given like all
that information as you gain and now
he's you know experienced your symptoms
again, you know, is there anything you
wish you could have done differently?
>> No, it's hard because in the game you
don't you don't really see it all and
the first one happens on their
sidelines. So probably you all have a
better perspective than anyone on our
sidelines. And so it's and and again he
he the way he talks to me about it was I
got hit and so I'm shaking up on the
play just from my football head and by
the time the doctors got out there I
felt fine. I got up and and was good.
Cleared everything and then post game
you get on the plane he come in this
morning and he's doing the right thing
and saying okay now I don't feel great
and so we'll put him back in the
protocol.
Mathematically, it's not that different
from last year, your odds to get into
the playoffs at this point. Do you guys
talk about anything like that?
>> We got to win. That's it's as simple as
that. I I don't know what the odds are.
I know they're not zero. Um and so what
I I told our guys, the odds aren't zero.
So, we're going to keep fighting, keep
scratching, keep calling. Um keep
approaching every week the way we've
been doing it. And we just got to win.
>> Offensive line.
>> Yeah.
>> Yep.
Yeah, I I thought they did a great job
in protection. Um Joe did a good job
buying some I mean sometimes I mean
really the the two sacks we given up the
last two weeks were corner blitzes.
Totally different situations. One was a
third down. You know the skies roll
pressure and the one against Baltimore
was a first second down under center
play action. Um so those are two that
that you know he's it's good calls by
the defense. The line's done a great job
in protection. um they've given him
time. The throw to Gaseki yesterday, we
blocked everyone we could. We got a
great squeeze on the right side. There's
an unblocked player we can't account
for. That's Joe's guy. Joe makes a miss
and hits Gaseki for touchdowns. So, I
thought everybody did a really good job
versus the pressure for the most part.
There's one or two that were tough. Um
and the line's been a big part of that.
And in the run game, they're giving us
exactly what we need in some key
situations. First down, it was a little
hard to to mix our runs with some of the
looks they were giving us that weren't
always successful. what I thought on
second down and third down, we did a
great job around the football and that's
a credit to the guys up front, the backs
and the tight ends, and I thought that
was really well executed. I know the
yards aren't there necessarily, but we
got we got what we needed out of them
when we needed it.
>> Is this the best defense you've ever had
this stretch of offensive line play? Is
it
>> It's hard for me to compare that. You
know, it's it's I think we're in a good
spot right now. We we've got a lot of
trust and confidence in those guys.
They've got trust and confidence in
themselves and each other. And so that's
where we're at right now. But it's
difficult for me to compare to years
past
seem to run with a lot of authority
yesterday.
>> I think he always does. You know, he's
he's really good. I think we got a great
combination the way that we utilize
those guys. And um the good news is
they're both good in all three phases of
playing running back. You know, in terms
of running, protecting, and receiving.
Uh they both show up in a lot of
different ways. And and so that's good
because we can utilize them. It's it's I
don't think it's very predictable for
the defense to know, okay, this guy's on
the field, this is going to happen
because they both shown that they're
good in all three phases. So, it's been
a big positive for us.
>> He talked about really want to be out
there and just kind of gutting it out as
much as he could. What was your reaction
to just how he kind of tried to fight
through whatever it was to
>> you said? Yeah. I mean, these guys want
to play football and and I, you know,
talking to T, talking to Jamar the week
before when they're sitting at home and
they're watching the game, it's painful
for them to have to watch, you know,
because they want to be a part of it and
they want to be a part of us winning and
they know they give us a great chance to
help us win. And so those guys have
fought through stuff for for all the
years we've had them, you know, you've
always if ever there was a chance that
they could play, they they're playing
and I appreciate it about T going back
in the protocol for the second time in
three weeks. Does that change the
timeline of how that how does that
>> We'll see. You know, it's it's again,
this is new information this morning, so
we'll keep working through it this week
and see what it lands.
>> Okay. Thank you.